Maryland Citizens Against State Executions; Records apap340
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1998-2013; Undated; 3; 1.4 cubic ft.
  - Printed Online Newspaper Articles, 2002-2003; 2008; 2012 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - DNA Innocence Newspaper Articles, 2002-2004 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Media, 2003 June (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Conover Case, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Curran, A G Joe, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - DNA, Innocence (Supplemental), 2003 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Kirk Bloodsworth, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Maryland State Attorneys, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - PG Co. Minister, 2003 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Oken, More About, 2003-2004 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Steele, Lt. Gov., 2003-2004 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Webster Care (and Resulting Fallout Out), 2003; 2005 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Abeokuta, Jamaal, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Burch Case, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Legal Issues, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - MD Balt. Co. Police Officer (Monty Smith), 2004 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - MD CASE Minutes, 2004 (Cd 5)
  - Oken Press Coverage - June 2004 Execution Date (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Evans, Vernon, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - MD CASE: Board Materials, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Race Appeal, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Wesley Baker, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Old News Clippings, 2004-2007; 2009; 2011 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - MD CASE Minutes, 2005 (Cd 6)
  - Baker & Evans Media, 2005-2006 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - PG Co. Articles, 2005-2006 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Corrections, 2005-2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - The Sun: Articles, 2006 November 06 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Board and Executive Committee Meeting Notes, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - UMD Study, 2006; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Baltimore City, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Press Archives - Bill, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Press/Articles, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49-50)
  - Baze v Recs/Lethal Injection articles, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Governor O'Malley, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - MD CASE General, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Misc Articles, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - MRJ 990, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Newspaper Ads, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Newspaper Archives, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Venable, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Articles, 2007-2008 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Lethal Injection/Baze articles, 2007-2008 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - MD CASE 990 FY, 2007-2008 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Session Articles, 2007-2008 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Press, 2007-2009 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Press, 2007-2008; 2011 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - ACLU Spy Report & Articles, 2008 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Commission Press, 2008 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - JFI Contract, 2008 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - MD CASE Board Meeting Minutes and Materials, 2008 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - MD Spying, 2008 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Kevin Jones Case, 2008-2009 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Newspaper: Gazette, 2009 February 27 (Flat-file 3)
  - Loan Agreement EJUSA, 2009 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Baltimore County, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - For Rion - Notes, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Frosh, Brian = Chair & Senate 3rd Proceedings Committee, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - MD CASE Documents, Undated (Cd 7)
  - Unlabeled Printed Digital Photograph, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)